## CAO XUÂN PHƯƠNG

81 Nguyen Cuu Van st, Binh Thanh DistrictHo Chi Minh City \_ +84967678629 \_ caophuong7989@gmail.com



## Personal Profile

Having more life experience and more ideas to apply technology into daily life has always been my desire. As a IT student from university, I'm looking forward an opportunity to become a part of the your projects in TMA, to meet and integrate with like-mind fellows, to improve my IT skills, to discover my better version.

Education	
Sep 2010 - Jun 2012	Student Hung Vuong Gifted High School
Sep 2012 - Dec 2016	Information System Engineering University of Information Technology
	Project —
Oct 2013 - Dec 2013	Application that uses Bayes's theorem to predict earthquake
	Discrete mathematics for computer science
Sep 2014 - Dec 2014	Warehouse managerment winform application
	Advanced Object-oriented programming in Windows environment
Feb 2015 - Apr 2015	Coffee online booking application
	Project managerment
Feb 2015 - May 2015	Online Banking web-based system(asp.Net)
	Analysis and Design System
Nov 2015 - Dec 2015	Crowdfunding website for University of Banking startup competition
	Work Experience
Jan 2014 - Sep 2014	
	University of Information Technology  Prepare and organize curricular activities e.g team-building, football league, seminars for student of this program
Jun 2014 - Aug 2014	Attendees of AIESEC Global Passport seasons 4&5
	Take chances to interactive workshops in English. Improve communication skills and cultural understanding.
Sep 2014 - Oct 2014	Attendees of AIESEC S.E.L.F season 2
	Develop self-leadership skill Increase seft-awareness
Dec 2014 - Feb 2015	Intern of AIESEC Exchange Internship in India

## AIESEC HoChiMinhCity

Project from NGO Samvedna,

Teaching English, other co-curricular activities to young kids. Develop teaching module to teach children between 6-17 years

Dec 2015 - Present Voluteer at FablabSaigon

Skills

IT Skills

Technical: Asp.NET, C#, SQL Server, HTML, CSS.

Language Skills

Having good working knowledge in English( proficient in reading and writting, listening)

Communication Skills

A good listener with other members in team and also communicate well. Offer new

ideas. Acquired experience about effective communication methods.

Managerial skills

Complete tasks on time. Adapt, pick up new skills quickly. Be innovative.

Awards

Jan 2012 - Jan 2013 Top 15% of students in faculty

Encouraging Scholarship

Jan 2012 - Jan 2013 Awarded to the top three performing students in 1st year

Top 3 student of AEP